hiphopblog.com 2012-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Hip Hop Blog

Safeguarding your privacy is serious business. **HipHopBlog.com** 's policy is simple: Except as provided in this statement, **HipHopBlog.com** will not disclose, sell or rent any personally identifiable information without proper consent. You, the **HipHopBlog.com** user, always have the final word on whether **HipHopBlog.com** knows who you are. It is your choice whether you wish to share personally identifiable information with **HipHopBlog.com**. We encourage you to consider sharing information with **HipHopBlog.com** only if you receive true value in exchange for that information.

Please use discretion when revealing personally identifiable information while using **HipHopBlog.com** tools, as it may be collected and used by unauthorized third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of **HipHopBlog.com**. In other words, if for some reason you post your home phone number in the **HipHopBlog.com** (which, by the way, you should NOT do), you're on your own.

Please take a minute to read our policy so that you understand your options, and how **HipHopBlog.com** collects, processes and shares information. If you have any questions about HipHopBlog.com's information practices, send an email to _HipHopBlog.com_.

### What information does HipHopBlog.com collect?

If you decide to _join_ **HipHopBlog.com** , registration is the only place where you are required to submit information about yourself. To become a member of **HipHopBlog.com** you need to submit your email address, gender, and zip code.

If you decide to join HipHopBlog.com's HIPHOPBLOG Alerts, you will need to submit your gender, birthday, city, state, zip-code and email address. This additional information is collected to customize information to you and is only used by HipHopBlog.com.

### Does HipHopBlog.com supplement the information it collects?

**HipHopBlog.com** appends such third party data to each member's record to understand demographics for a zip or postal code or set of zip/postal codes.

### What are cookies and how does HipHopBlog.com use them?

The main function of cookies is to connect members with their stored account information so that **HipHopBlog.com** can deliver better and more personalized service. Cookies do not enable the **HipHopBlog.com** staff to access personally identifiable information that you haven't already provided.

Read this article on Cookie Central for more information on Cookies.

### How does HipHopBlog.com use member information?

**HipHopBlog.com** uses information collected from you and other members primarily to provide more personalized service and advertising, and to learn more about its audience demographic. **HipHopBlog.com** also collects market research data in order to generate sales to corporate clients. Market research data are always anonymous and are never used to sell anything to individual respondents based on their personal responses.

### What information does HipHopBlog.com log?

**HipHopBlog.com** logs information automatically transmitted from your browser (URL of the Web page you were on before coming to **HipHopBlog.com** , IP address and browser version); information you submit through registration, forms for optional programs, surveys and other entries; and communications transmitted through **HipHopBlog.com** tools.

### How does HipHopBlog.com secure collected information?

**HipHopBlog.com** makes every effort to make sure your information is secure. Extremely sensitive information, like credit card numbers, is always transmitted in encrypted form. Your **HipHopBlog.com** account is password-protected so that only you and authorized **HipHopBlog.com** employees can access your information.

If you lost your password to the HipHopBlog.com, you can retrieve it here. You will need to have access to the e-mail account that you registered with.

### With whom does HipHopBlog.com share information?

When you submit information to **HipHopBlog.com** , it isn't shared with anyone unless you opt-in for it.

### What is HipHopBlog.com's opt-in/out policy?

During registration you choose whether to receive correspondence from **HipHopBlog.com**. This information lives on your profile where you can, at any point, easily edit it to indicate that you have changed your mind. As for promotions, contests, submission opportunities and programs, you will not be included unless you opt-in.

### How can HipHopBlog.com members edit their personal information?

**HipHopBlog.com** believes strongly in giving you the ability to access and edit your personal information. To update your personal info, click here.
